A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, First Administration, Series 37.1 FA439
Rockefeller Archive Center
- First Administration, 1959-1962; 1; 171 microform reels
  - Legislation (Reel 71, Reel 72, Reel 73, Reel 74, Reel 75, Reel 76, Reel 77, Reel 78, Reel 79)
    - 1959 (Reel 76, Reel 77, Reel 78)
      - State
        - Public Safety (Reel 77)
        - Public Utilities (Reel 77)
        - Public Works (Reel 77)
        - Welfare (Reel 77)
        - Youth (Reel 77)
        - General
          - 1959 March-December (Reel 77)
          - 1959 January-February (Reel 78)
    - General, undated (Reel 78, Reel 79)
      - Federal (Reel 78)
        - Committees (Reel 78)
        - Meetings (Reel 78)
        - General (Reel 78)
      - State
        - Committees (Reel 78)
          - Commerce & Economic Development (Reel 78)
          - Constitutional Revision (Reel 78)
          - Fire Laws (Reel 78)
          - Health Insurance Plan (Reel 78)
          - Industrial & Labor Conditions (Reel 78)
          - Interstate Cooperation (Reel 78)
          - Maryland Act (Workmen's Compensation) (Reel 78)
          - Motor Vehicles & Traffic Safety (Reel 78)
          - Natural Resources (Reel 78)
          - Affairs of New York City (Reel 78)
          - Preservation & Restoration of Historical Sites (Reel 78)
          - Privacy of Communications (Reel 78)
          - Publication of Offensive & Obscene Material (Reel 78)
          - School Finances (Reel 78)
          - State's Economy (Reel 78)
          - Village & Town Fiscal Affairs (Reel 78)
          - General (Reel 78)
        - Messages (Reel 79)
          - Annual Message (Reel 79)
          - Budget Message (Reel 79)
          - Special Messages (Reel 79)
        - General (Reel 79)
          - Certificate of Intent (Reel 79)
          - Certificate of Allocation (Reel 79)
          - Special Sessions (Reel 79)
          - General (Reel 79)
  - Licensing (Reel 79, Reel 80, Reel 81)
    - Accountancy (Reel 79, Reel 80)
      - 1962 (Reel 79)
      - 1959 (Reel 80)
    - Bingo (Reel 80)
    - Cabaret Employees (Reel 80)
    - Chiropractors (Reel 80)
    - Liquor (Reel 80, Reel 81)
      - General (Reel 80)
        - 1962 (Reel 80)
      - Buffalo Taverns
        - 1961 June 30-1962 (Reel 80)
        - 1959-1961 June 29 (Reel 81)
      - General (Reel 81)
        - 1959-1961 (Reel 81)
    - Medical (Reel 81)
      - Foreign Medical Students (Reel 81)
      - General (Reel 81)
    - Nurse (Reel 81)
    - Real Estate (Reel 81)
    - Teacher (Reel 81)
    - General (Reel 81)
  - Mental Hygiene (Reel 81, Reel 82, Reel 83)
    - Department of (Reel 81)
      - Governor's Conference on the Defense of Insanity (Reel 81)
      - Department of Psychiatric Aid Awards (Reel 81)
      - General
        - 1961-1962 (Reel 81)
        - 1959-1960 (Reel 82)
    - Institutions (Reel 82, Reel 83)
      - Binghamton State Hospital (Reel 82)
      - Brooklyn State Hospital (Reel 82)
      - Buffalo State Hospital (Reel 82)
      - Central Islip (Reel 82)
      - Craig Colony (Reel 82)
      - Creedmoor (Reel 82)
      - Harlem Valley State Hospital (Reel 82)
      - Hudson River State Hospital (Reel 82)
      - Huntington (Reel 82)
      - Kings Park State Hospital (Reel 82)
      - Letchworth Village (Reel 82)
      - Marcy State Hospital (Reel 82)
      - Middletown State Hospital (Reel 82)
      - Mout McGregor (Reel 82)
      - Newark State Hospital (Reel 82)
      - Pilgrim State Hospital (Reel 83)
      - Rochester State Hospital (Reel 83)
      - Rockland State Hospital (Reel 83)
      - Rome State School (Reel 83)
      - Syracuse State School (Reel 83)
      - Willard State Hospital (Reel 83)
      - Willbrook State School (Reel 83)
      - Others (Reel 83)
      - General (Reel 83)
    - General (Reel 83)
      - Emotionally Disturbed Blind Children (Reel 83)
      - Research Institute on Mental Retardation (Reel 83)
      - General (Reel 83)
  - Military & Naval (Reel 83, Reel 84, Reel 85)
    - State (Reel 83, Reel 84, Reel 85)
      - Military & Naval Affairs (Reel 83)
        - National Guard (Reel 83)
          - General (Reel 84)
        - Armories, New York City
          - 1959-1960 (Reel 83)
          - 1961-1962 (Reel 84)
        - General (Reel 84)
        - General
          - Military Reservations
            - Brooklyn Army Terminal (Reel 84)
            - Camp Drum (Reel 84)
            - Griffiss Air Force Base (Reel 84)
            - Mitchell Field
              - 1961 February 3-1962 (Reel 84)
              - 1959-1961 February 2 (Reel 85)
            - New York Naval Shipyard (Reel 85)
            - Sampson Airforce Base (Reel 85)
            - Scotis Naval Depot (Reel 85)
            - General (Reel 85)
    - Federal (Reel 85)
      - U.S. Army (Reel 85)
      - U.S. Air Force (Reel 85)
        - Civil Air Patrol (Reel 85)
        - General (Reel 85)
      - U.S. Navy (Reel 85)
      - General (Reel 85)
  - Parks & Recreational Facilities (Reel 85, Reel 86)
    - Parks (Reel 85, Reel 86)
      - Breezy Point (Reel 85)
      - Central Park (Reel 85)
      - Long Point (Reel 85)
      - Massapequa Park (Reel 85)
      - Renselaer County (Reel 85)
      - Short Beach
        - 1960 October 6-1962 (Reel 85)
        - 1959-1960 October 5 (Reel 86)
      - Others (Reel 86)
    - Winter Sports (Reel 86)
      - Gore Mountain (Reel 86)
      - Mount Van Hoevenberg Bobsled Run (Reel 86)
      - General (Reel 86)
    - Governor's Program (Reel 86)
    - General (Reel 86)
  - Personnel Administration (Reel 86, Reel 87, Reel 88, Reel 89, Reel 90)
    - Civil Service Department (Reel 86)
      - Classification & Compensation (Reel 86)
        - Reclassification & Reallocation (Reel 86)
      - Examinations (Reel 86)
        - Certifications (Reel 86)
        - Disqualifications (Reel 86)
        - Placement (Reel 86)
        - Veterans Preference (Reel 86)
        - General (Reel 86)
      - Merit Award (Reel 86)
      - New York State Personnel Council (Reel 86)
    - Personnel Services (Reel 87)
      - Training Intern Program (Reel 87)
      - Management Program (Reel 87)
      - Visual Aid Program (Reel 87)
      - General (Reel 87)
    - General (Reel 87)
    - Resolutions (Reel 87)
    - State Employees (Reel 87, Reel 88, Reel 89)
      - Attendance Rules (Reel 87)
        - Special Holidays (Reel 87)
        - General (Reel 87)
      - Code of Ethics (Reel 88)
        - Joseph Carlino (Reel 88)
        - General (Reel 88)
      - Governor's Commission to Study Condon-Wadlin Law (Reel 88)
      - Condon-Wadlin Law (Reel 88)
      - Grievances
        - Payroll Problems (Reel 88)
        - Appointments (Reel 88)
        - Board Decisions (Reel 88)
        - Reinstatement (Reel 88)
        - Termination (Reel 88)
        - General (Reel 88)
        - Hearing Reporters (Reel 88)
        - Outside Jobs (Reel 88)
        - Incentive Awards (Reel 88)
        - Parking (Reel 88)
        - Pensions (Reel 88)
        - Retirement (Reel 88)
        - Salaries
          - 1961 July-1962 (Reel 88)
          - 1959-1961 June (Reel 89)
        - Saving Bond Campaign (Reel 89)
        - Security Risk (Reel 89)
        - General (Reel 89)
    - Teachers (Reel 89)
      - Pension & Retirement (Reel 89)
      - General (Reel 89)
    - Local (Reel 89)
      - City (Reel 89)
        - New York City (Reel 89)
          - Police (Reel 89)
          - General (Reel 89)
        - General (Reel 89)
      - County (Reel 89)
      - Town & Village (Reel 89)
    - General (Reel 89, Reel 90)
      - Governor's Comm. on Investment of Public Pensions Fund (Reel 89)
      - General (Reel 90)
  - Politics (Reel 90)
    - General (Reel 90)
      - 1962 Governorship (Reel 90)
      - Fund Raising Campaign (Reel 90)
      - General (Reel 90)
  - Property (Reel 90, Reel 91)
    - Federal (Reel 90)
      - Surplus Property Program (Reel 90)
    - Acquisition & Purchase (Reel 90, Reel 91)
      - Conservation
        - Town of Middlebury (Reel 90)
        - Highways (Reel 90)
          - Sunrise Highway (Reel 90)
          - Wantaugh-Oyster Bay Expressway (Reel 90)
        - Parks
          - Cedar Grove Beach (Reel 90)
          - Marshall Field Estate (Reel 90)
          - Mongaup Pond (Reel 90)
          - Sampson (Reel 90)
          - Sullivan County (Reel 90)
          - General
            - 1962 (Reel 90)
            - 1959-1961 (Reel 91)
        - Power Authority (Reel 91)
        - Others (Reel 91)
        - General (Reel 91)
    - General (Reel 91)
      - Ellis Island (Reel 91)
      - Inspector II (Reel 91)
      - State University Site (Reel 91)
      - General (Reel 91)
  - Public Safety (Reel 91, Reel 92, Reel 93, Reel 94)
    - Federal (Reel 91)
    - State Police (Reel 91, Reel 92)
      - Division of Complaints (Reel 91)
      - Increase in Personnel (Reel 91)
      - Reports (Reel 91)
      - Rules & Regulations (Reel 91)
      - Troopers (Reel 91)
        - Appointments (Reel 91)
        - Complaints (Reel 92)
        - Graduation (Reel 92)
        - Captain Lawson (Reel 92)
        - Letters of Commendation (Reel 92)
        - Reinstatement (Reel 92)
        - General (Reel 92)
      - Use of Files for Television Series (Reel 92)
      - General (Reel 92)
    - Highway Safety (Reel 92, Reel 93, Reel 94)
      - Citizens Council Finance &Advisory Committee (Reel 92)
      - Citizen Council on Traffic Safety (Reel 92)
      - Drinking Drivers (Reel 92)
      - Holiday Weekends (Reel 92)
      - Interdepartmental Committee on Traffic Safety (Reel 92)
      - Seat Safety (Reel 92)
      - 7 Point Program (Reel 92)
      - Specific Routes (Reel 93)
      - Speed Limits (Reel 93)
      - Traffic Safety Policy Coordination Committee (Reel 93)
      - Traffic Signals (Reel 93)
      - General
        - 1959 August-1962 (Reel 93)
        - 1959 January-June (Reel 94)
    - State (Reel 94)
      - Amusement Rides (Reel 94)
      - Crime (Reel 94)
      - Crime & Law Enforcement (Reel 94)
      - Fire Prevention Conference (Reel 94)
      - Firearms (Reel 94)
      - Industrial Safety (Reel 94)
      - Local Police (Reel 94)
      - Water Safety (Reel 94)
      - Weapons (Reel 94)
    - General (Reel 94)
  - Public Utilities (Reel 94, Reel 95, Reel 96, Reel 97, Reel 98, Reel 99, Reel 100)
    - Communications (Reel 94)
    - Fuel (Reel 94, Reel 95)
      - Gas
        - Discontinuance of Service (Plattsburgh) (Reel 94)
        - Rates (Reel 95)
        - General (Reel 95)
      - Petroleum Products (Reel 95)
        - H.P. Sears (Reel 95)
        - General (Reel 95)
      - General (Reel 95)
    - Power (Reel 95, Reel 96, Reel 97)
      - Atomic Development
        - Governor's Plan (Reel 95)
        - Jamestown Reactor (Reel 95)
        - Nuclear Testing (Reel 95)
        - Advisory Committee (Reel 96)
        - Office of (Reel 96)
        - Western New York Nuclear Service Center (Reel 96)
        - General (Reel 96)
      - General
        - Electric Rates (Reel 96)
        - Conjunctional Billing (Reel 96)
        - Committee on Power Resources (Reel 96)
        - General
          - 1961-1962 (Reel 96)
          - 1959-1960 (Reel 97)
    - Transportation (Reel 97, Reel 98, Reel 99)
      - Railroads
        - Delaware & Hudson Railroad (Reel 97)
        - Erie & Lackaranna Railroad (Reel 97)
        - Full Crew Law (Reel 97)
        - Hudson & Manhattan Railroad (Reel 97)
        - Long Island Railroad (Reel 97)
        - New Haven Railroad (Reel 97)
        - New York Central Railroad
          - 1961-1962 (Reel 97)
          - 1959-1960 (Reel 98)
        - Tri-State Governor's Meeting (Reel 98)
        - General (Reel 98)
      - Buses (Reel 98)
      - Ferries (Reel 98)
      - Subways (Reel 98)
      - Commuter Problems
        - 1960-1962 (Reel 98)
        - 1959 (Reel 99)
      - Office of Transportation (Reel 99)
      - General (Reel 99)
        - Tri-State Transportation Meeting (Reel 99)
        - General (Reel 99)
    - Public Service (Reel 99, Reel 100)
      - Public Service Commission (Reel 99)
      - Public Service Commission (Reel 100)
  - Public Works (Reel 100, Reel 101, Reel 102, Reel 103, Reel 104, Reel 105, Reel 106)
    - Highways (Reel 100, Reel 101, Reel 102, Reel 103, Reel 104)
      - Aurora Expressway (Reel 100)
      - Clearview Expressway (Reel 100)
      - Cross Bronx Expressway (Reel 100)
      - Cross Westchester Expressway (Reel 100)
      - Interstate Route (Reel 100)
        - #84 (Reel 100)
        - #81 (Reel 100)
        - #87 (Reel 100)
      - Route (Reel 100)
        - #15 (Reel 100)
        - #57 (Reel 100)
      - Fire Island (Reel 100)
      - Grand Central Parkway (Reel 100)
      - Kensington Expressway (Reel 101)
      - Lake Ontario State Parkway (Reel 101)
      - Local Roads (Reel 101)
      - Long Island Expressway (Reel 101)
      - Narrows Bridge (Reel 101)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Bridge (Reel 101)
      - Niagara Falls-Lewiston Bridge (Reel 101)
      - Route #9 (Reel 101)
      - Route #9N (Reel 101)
      - Northway (Reel 101)
      - Route #110 (Amityville) (Reel 101)
      - Route #133 (Reel 101)
      - Poughkeepsie Arterial (Reel 102)
      - Quaker Ridge Road (Reel 102)
      - Scenic Highway (St. Lawrence) (Reel 102)
      - Route (Reel 102)
        - #7 (Reel 102)
        - #17 (Reel 102)
        - #60 (Reel 102)
      - Slingerlands By-Pass (Reel 102)
      - Southern Tier Expressway (Reel 102)
      - Sprain Brook Expressway (Reel 102)
      - Sunrise Highway (Reel 102)
      - Syosset (Woodbury Road) (Reel 102)
      - Taconic Parkway (Reel 102)
      - Thruway (Reel 102)
      - Route
        - #28 (Reel 102)
        - #25A (Reel 102)
        - #23 (Reel 102)
        - #22
          - 1961 February 8-1962 (Reel 102)
          - 1959-1961 February 7 (Reel 103)
        - #240 (Reel 103)
      - Union Bridge Canal (Reel 103)
      - Utica North (South Arterial Highway) (Reel 103)
      - Wantaugh (Oyster Bay Expressway) (Reel 103)
      - Westchester County Parkway (Reel 103)
      - World's Fair Site (Reel 103)
      - General
        - 1962 (Reel 103)
        - 1959-1961 (Reel 104)
    - Specific Topics
      - Billboards (Reel 104)
      - Federal Highway Program (Reel 104)
      - Grade Crossing Elimination (Reel 104)
        - Town of Marcy (Reel 104)
        - General (Reel 104)
      - Snow Removal (Reel 105)
      - Tree Removal (Reel 105)
      - Use of Screened Gravel (Reel 105)
      - Weed Control (Reel 105)
      - General (Reel 105)
    - Department of (Reel 105)
      - Stockpile (Reel 105)
      - General (Reel 105)
    - Buildings
      - State Office Building at Buffalo (Reel 105)
      - Campus Site (Reel 105)
      - New York State Capitol (Reel 105)
      - Stock School Plan (Reel 105)
      - General (Reel 106)
    - Canals & Waterways (Reel 106)
      - Barge Canal Erie (Reel 106)
      - Canal Fire (Reel 106)
      - Island Inlet (Reel 106)
      - General (Reel 106)
  - Regrets (Reel 106, Reel 107, Reel 108, Reel 109, Reel 110, Reel 111, Reel 112, Reel 113, Reel 114, Reel 115, Reel 116, Reel 117, Reel 118, Reel 119, Reel 120, Reel 121, Reel 122, Reel 123)
    - 1962 (Reel 106, Reel 107, Reel 108, Reel 109, Reel 110)
      - 1962 November 8-December 31 (Reel 106)
      - 1962 August 22-November 7 (Reel 107)
      - 1962 May 19-August 21 (Reel 108)
      - 1962 February 15-May 18 (Reel 109)
      - 1962 January 1-February 14 (Reel 110)
      - undated (Reel 110)
    - 1961 (Reel 110, Reel 111, Reel 112, Reel 113, Reel 114)
      - 1961 January 1-February 7 (Reel 110)
      - 1961 February 8-May 3 (Reel 111)
      - 1961 May 4-July 14 (Reel 112)
      - 1961 July 15-October 21 (Reel 113)
      - 1961 October 22-December 31 (Reel 114)
    - 1960 (Reel 114, Reel 115, Reel 116, Reel 117, Reel 118)
      - undated (Reel 114)
      - 1960 January 1-6 (Reel 114)
      - 1960 January 7-March 26 (Reel 115)
      - 1960 March 27-May 24 (Reel 116)
      - 1960 May 25-September 15 (Reel 117)
      - 1960 September 16-December 31 (Reel 118)
    - 1959 (Reel 118, Reel 119, Reel 120, Reel 121, Reel 122, Reel 123)
      - 1959 January 1-31 (Reel 118)
      - 1959 February 1-May 10 (Reel 119)
      - 1959 May 11-July 10 (Reel 120)
      - 1959 July 11-October 7 (Reel 121)
      - 1959 October 8-November 30 (Reel 122)
      - 1959 December 1-31 (Reel 123)
      - undated (Reel 123)
  - Resignations & Vacancies (Reel 123, Reel 124)
    - State (Reel 123, Reel 124)
      - Authorities & Commissions (Reel 123)
        - General (Reel 123)
        - County (Reel 123)
        - Conservation Department (Reel 123)
          - State Council of Parks (Robert Moses) (Reel 123)
        - Executive Department (Reel 123)
          - Executive Chamber (Reel 123)
          - General (Reel 123)
        - Labor Department (Reel 123)
        - Mental Hygiene (Reel 123)
        - Social Welfare (Reel 123)
        - State University (Reel 123)
      - Other Departments (Reel 124)
      - Judiciary (Reel 124)
      - Miscellaneous (Reel 124)
  - NAR Personal (Reel 124, Reel 125, Reel 126, Reel 127, Reel 128, Reel 129, Reel 130, Reel 131, Reel 132, Reel 133)
    - A-BU (Reel 124)
      Scope and Contents note
      includes: Anniversary and birthday greetings
    - Bur-Condolences (Reel 125)
      includes: Christmas cards and greetings and condolences
    - Condolences-Gifts (Reel 126)
      includes: Notes of condolence and congratulations, and Easter and Fathers Day cards.
    - Gifts
      - Books (Reel 127)
      - Others (Reel 128)
    - Har-Li (Reel 129)
      includes: Notes to those who attended his inaugural ball
    - Lo-Roc (Reel 130)
      includes: New Year greetings, photographs and portraits
    - Ros-Thank You (Reel 131)
      includes: Thank You notes for trips taken with NAR
    - Thank You (Reel 132)
      includes: More Thank You notes for trips taken with NAR
    - Thank You-Z (Reel 133)
      includes: Yet More Thank You notes and Thanksgiving, Valentine and Wedding cards.
  - Statements (Reel 133, Reel 134, Reel 135, Reel 136, Reel 137, Reel 138, Reel 139)
    - 1962 (Reel 133, Reel 134, Reel 135)
      - 1962 December (Reel 133)
      - 1962 May-November (Reel 134)
      - 1962 January-April (Reel 135)
    - 1961 (Reel 136, Reel 135)
      - 1961 July-December (Reel 135)
      - 1961 January-June (Reel 136)
    - 1960 (Reel 136, Reel 137, Reel 138)
      - 1960 November-December (Reel 136)
      - 1960 February-October (Reel 137)
      - 1960 January (Reel 138)
    - 1959 (Reel 138, Reel 139)
      - 1959 May-December (Reel 138)
      - 1959 January-April (Reel 139)
  - Veterans (Reel 139, Reel 140)
    - Institutions (Reel 139, Reel 140)
      - Chastle Point Hospital (Reel 139)
      - Mt. McGregor
        - 1959 November-1962 (Reel 139)
        - 1959 January 1-October 29 (Reel 140)
    - Curtailment of Counseling Services (Reel 140)
    - Division of (Reel 140)
    - General (Reel 140)
      - Veterans Bonus (Reel 140)
        - Korea (Reel 140)
        - Others (Reel 140)
      - General (Reel 140)
  - Welfare (Reel 140, Reel 141, Reel 142, Reel 143)
    - Institutions (Reel 140, Reel 141, Reel 142)
      - Hudson State Training School for Girls (Reel 140)
      - Industry State Agriculture School (Reel 140)
      - New Hampton (Reel 140)
      - Warwick Training School (Reel 140)
      - Women's Relief Corps Home (Oxford) (Reel 141)
      - Others (Reel 141)
      - General
        - 1961-1962 (Reel 141)
        - 1959-1960 (Reel 142)
    - Department of (Reel 142)
      - Commission for the Blind (Reel 142)
      - Board of Social Workers (Reel 142)
      - Committee on Charitable Solicitations (Reel 142)
      - Indian Affairs (Reel 142)
      - New York City Welfare Department Scandal (Reel 142)
      - Surplus Food Program (Reel 142)
      - General (Reel 142)
    - General (Reel 142, Reel 143)
      - Adoption (Reel 142)
      - Assistance Cases (Reel 142)
      - City of Newburgh
        - 1961 August-1962 (Reel 142)
        - 1959-1961 July (Reel 143)
      - Refugees (Reel 143)
      - Residency (Reel 143)
        - Committee (Reel 143)
        - Unanswered (Reel 143)
        - General (Reel 143)
      - General (Reel 143)
  - Youth (Reel 144, Reel 145, Reel 146, Reel 147, Reel 148)
    - Division of (Reel 144)
      - Young American Medals for Bravery (Reel 144)
      - General (Reel 144)
    - General (Reel 144, Reel 145, Reel 146, Reel 147, Reel 148)
      - Governor's Committee on Children & Youth (Reel 144)
      - Interdepartmental Committee on Youth (Reel 144)
      - Juvenile Delinquency
        - Governor's 6-point program (Reel 144)
        - Meeting, 1959 September 8 (Reel 144)
        - Task Force (Reel 144)
        - General (Reel 144)
        - Form 1 (Reel 145)
        - Form 2
          - 1959 October-1962 (Reel 145)
          - 1959 January-September (Reel 146)
        - Form 3 (Reel 146)
        - Form 4 (Reel 146)
        - Form 5 (Reel 146)
        - Form 6 (Reel 146)
      - New York Mirror Youth Program (Reel 146)
      - October Youth Conference (Queens), 1961 (Reel 146)
      - Local Youth Centers (Reel 146)
      - Puerto Rican Community Self Help Program (Reel 146)
      - Sale of Liquor to Minors
        - 1962 July-December (Reel 146)
        - 1959-1962 June (Reel 147)
      - School Drop Out Program (Reel 147)
      - Start Program (Reel 147)
      - Youth & Work Conference, 1962 January 23 (Reel 147)
      - White House Conference (Reel 147)
        - Appointments (Reel 147)
        - Reports (Reel 147)
        - General (Reel 147)
      - Youth Camp Program (Reel 147)
      - Youth Court Act (Reel 147)
      - Youth Fitness President's Council (Reel 148)
        - General (Reel 148)
      - General (Reel 148)
  - Organizations
    Arrangement
    Alphabetical by name of organization.
    - Albany - American Federation of Labor (Reel 148)
    - American Federation - American: C. (Reel 149)
    - American: D - Associations (Reel 150)
    - Avenue - Cam (Reel 151)
    - Carnegie - Citizens Committee for Children (Reel 152)
    - Citizens Committee for Children, 1962-1969 June (Reel 152)
    - Citizens Committee for Children, 1959 January-May (Reel 153)
    - Citizens Committee for Children - Community Service Society (Reel 153)
    - Community - Council (Reel 154)
    - County - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies. (Reel 155)
    - Federation of Woman's Republican Clubs - Governor's Conference: Civil Defense (1962) (Reel 156)
    - Governor's Conference: Civil Defense (1959-1961) - General (1962), 1959-1962 (Reel 157)
    - General (1959-1961) - Institute of World Affairs, Inc. (Reel 158)
    - Institute - Ku (Reel 159)
    - L - Mi (Reel 160)
    - Mil - National Maritime Union of America (Reel 161)
    - National Merit Scholarship - New York Association (Reel 162)
    - New York Board of Rabbis - New York State Catholic Welfare Committee (Reel 163)
    - New York State Citizens Committee for the Public Schools - New York State: Others, E-L (Reel 164)
    - New York State: Others, M-O - Organizations: Po (Reel 165)
    - Prison - Republican National Committee (Reel 166)
    - New York County Republican Committee - Savings Banks (Reel 167)
    - Sc - Uniformed Fire Officers Association (Reel 168)
    - Uniformed Sanitationmen's Association - Westchester County Grand Jurors Association (Reel 169)
    - Westchester - Z (Reel 170)
  - Supplemental material (Reel 171)
    - Supplementary Film File (Reel 171)
      includes: Material on the State University and the Department of Motor Vehicles